This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison Impel Down,
forming an unlikely alliance with Buggy the Cloud.
Luffy heads to the second level of the prison, the floor of Wild Beast from Hell.
There he encounters Mr. Three, a former Baroque works agent,
that continues his descent alongside his unwilling allies.
My, my. Sounds like there's a lot of fun going on in the world.
Shinbei, Ace, look, do you get it?
This world is full of dozens of second placers,
silver medalists who could never defeat Roger and Whitebeard,
all holding back their tears.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Chief Guard Saul Death's Track! Level 3 Starvation Hell!
Monitor room, we've arrived at level two.
Can you see the image on screen?
We can.
Keep us posted on what you find down there.
Roger that.
What happened here?
Look at the size of this hole.
It's so big, even the sphinx could have fallen through it.
What in the hell is Straw Hat Luffy looking for?
Huh?
That does not look good.
I don't know how they got the keys, but the prisoners on level two
are out of their cells.
Don't tell me Straw Hat and his friends did this.
Those guards are in trouble down there.
Let's hear it for our savior, Captain Buggy.
Now it's payback time.
Level two reporting in.
We need backup here.
The prisoners are all free.
I repeat.
Quick!
Luguri to level two!
Hey!
Good news, men.
We know what Straw Hat's doing.
Yeah?
Who told you?
Fleet Admiral Sengoku himself just sent word to us.
Huh?
Little did we know, Monkey D. Luffy and our condemned prisoner, Port Garciace, have more in common
than the D in their names.
It turns out they're brothers!
Huh?
Hold on.
Are you saying he's trying to stop the public execution?
Break in and make it out with his brother before we can transport him?
What else could it be?
That would explain why he keeps going down.
We were so focused on Whitebeard's attack, we let him sneak inside.
If he manages to pull this off, all hell's gonna break loose.
We've gotta stop him!
Inform Warden Magellan immediately and get that riot on level two under control.
Now!
Think this is funny?
Do you?
Hum!
We're at a crossroads that could change the future of the sea!
Yet that troublemaking grandson of yours seems to undermine our efforts at every turn!
Just like it in his lobby!
This symbol represents the unity of over 170 nations!
A power that spans the Four Seas and the Grand Line!
This is the world itself!
Do you realize how strong our organization is?
Do you realize how devoted we are to capturing her?
If that's Robin's enemy, then I know what to do.
Sniper King.
Hm?
Shoot down that flag.
Roger!
This is my new weapon!
A massive slingshot by the name of Kabuto!
Behold its awesome power!
Special attack!
Firebird Star!
No way!
They're the celestial dragons!
Now you're annoying me too!
Hm?
No way!
Then they're celestial dragons!
Then they're Celestial Dragons!
Now you're annoying me too!
Damn it!
This is unprecedented, I say!
Let this sink in!
We haven't had a single breakout in Impel Denham in the past 20 years!
The Golden Lion was the last.
No one else has challenged these walls from the inside or the outside.
Impel Denham is more than a prison.
It's a symbol of unyielding justice with an iron-tight reputation
that Straw Hat is attempting to tarnish.
And to make it even worse, he's the grandson of a Marine!
And Mrs. Boy, I'm so proud of him!
Damn that Kuba.
He said he took care of the Straw Hat crew at the Sabaluri Archipelago.
I should have known better than to trust that fool!
Man's one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
What do you expect?
What I want to know is how he was able to get through the defenses we've got set up.
You think you flew here?
That's enough!
If you weren't known all over the Grand Line as the hero of the Navy, Doc,
I'd make you take responsibility for your family myself!
Go ahead! Lock me up! Execute me! It won't change a thing!
Nothing! You hear me? It's too late!
Laugh it up while you can!
But a blow like this to our reputation will have serious repercussions!
Sudo and I have tried to keep this under wraps, but there's only so much we can do!
Hey! Those are mine, dammit! No fear!
Get up already!
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah Aaaaaaah Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Aaaaah!
Oh-oh!
Ow! Ow!
This floor feels like a energía!
So are we in the desert?
It's hot.
Why is it so quiet?
Level three.
Oh, I never wanted to end up here.
Cut!
If I have to go to one more crappy place with you, I'll lose my mind!
He's taking a cat now.
Wow, that's real funny!
This place is especially bad for someone like me.
I'm a wax man, after all.
Big place.
So where are the stairs down?
I haven't a clue.
Your body here is going to melt if we don't get moving soon.
Well, all right, then off we go.
I think I thought maybe we should have just sat down and died.
Don't waste your energy complaining.
I won't carry you if you collapse.
Hey, look, it's grilled chicken time!
That is not natural.
A hummingbird fluttered down from above.
It was grilled in the open.
How hot is it here?
This is good.
You're missing out.
No, thank you.
I wish I could eat that lion from upstairs.
I bet this heat could barbecue him.
That thing talked like a human.
Are you serious?
At this rate, he's going to eat us next.
Look, you see that?
What, the jail cells?
Who cares?
How thick can it you get, kid?
We can hide from the sun inside there.
I'm prisoners who can lead us to the stairs.
Whoa, I didn't think of that.
Man, you're the smartest.
Damn straight I am.
Hey, Mr. Three, quick, make some keys.
I'm afraid there's just no place to hide.
Hey, could you tell me where the...
A miserable sight if I've ever seen one.
You wouldn't think looking at them now,
but the prisoners on this floor were all hardened criminals
commanding bounties of over 50 million berries.
Beneath here is the burning heat hell cooking the ground.
Also, these men are deprived of food and water,
leaving them half dead.
A shell of their former selves.
This is level three, the starvation hell.
Yes, now you know why this floor is covered
with what appears to be sand.
Oh, no.
Alas, yes.
Chances are what you're standing on
are the remains of prisoners
who have completely dried up.
If we remain in this place too long,
we'll become sand beneath someone's feet
just like they did.
In other words, let's move
while we have the sweat to spare.
Okay, then let's go to level four already.
Oh, seriously?
Not that way.
We need to take the stairs to the left.
We do?
No, we should take the pass on the right.
Are you making this up?
Reporting in, sir.
The targets are proceeding to the back.
Understood.
Keep an eye on them for now.
Be patient.
All is going according to plan.
Haven't you been able to contact Warden Magellan yet?
No, not yet, sir.
What about the Blugori?
They headed off to catch the invaders
with their commanders, sir.
Damn it.
The security of Impel Down
shouldn't fall to pieces this easily.
Why?
Why are we back where we started?
Because we went in a circle, I guess.
Quit being so relaxed.
We're having a crisis here.
I knew we should have gone to the right.
It's hot here.
I sure hope we get to level four soon.
Go by yourself.
I'm getting out of here.
But you said we were going to say these together.
You have to show me the way.
That was the deal.
I never said that.
Neither of us did.
You're just making stuff up
because that's what you want to hear.
I could have sworn you said that.
They've returned and are in place, sir.
Good.
Then draw the net.
Yes, sir.
Fine.
I don't need to.
What is this thing?
A trap, obviously.
Dammit, we're done more.
I think it's made of fire.
What's with this?
I should be able to use my chop chop powers.
This must be lined with C-prism stone.
I fear they'll give us more than a slap on the wrist
for our little attempted escape.
We'll be tortured to death.
We've captured the invader Straw Hat Luffy
along with two others.
What do you mean two others?
I've got a name.
Don't antagonize them, buggy.
You'll only make it worse.
And it's more than bad enough already.
Crap!
There's got to be some way to rip this net.
The guards end of the courtier coming.
Put the C-prism stone handcuffs on them.
Yes, sir.
Who's this guy?
This guy is called Saldeth.
Salt breath, huh?
You better change your diet.
No!
That's not what I said.
Pay attention.
It's Saldeth.
Got it?
Right.
Sardine head.
No!
Get it right!
What's wrong with you?
Hmm?
At any rate, there's no point in you resisting us.
You're in a highly secure underwater prison,
so needless to say, there's nowhere for you to run.
Hmm.
You know, you're fortunate that I was the one who captured you.
There are four other guards prowling around on the floors beyond this one.
And they're demons.
Hmm.
He's right.
This little guy's downright cute compared to what's down there.
If only we'd turned right, we were so close.
It wouldn't have mattered.
They both circle around and we were watching you the entire time,
so if you hadn't ended up in this trap,
we would have gotten you with another one.
That's how it is.
Hmm.
Vangoli.
Bianco.
Ah!
Chief the Sphinx!
Pasta!
He's moved on them past us now!
Oh, no!
Ah!
Belfast!
His face is awake!
Oh, no!
He's gonna break the net!
Be careful, men!
They can't escape, especially not straw hat!
Ah!
Deep prime load on!
Did he say that one yet?
I don't even care anymore!
Ah!
Hey, I'm free!
Still hot, but at least I can run away!
After them!
Ah!
Oh!
Stop隊!
Ah!
Hey, where'd they go?
Uh!
Ah!
Come on, Mr. Three, hurry up.
I can't move quickly in this heat.
They climbed up the net.
Good thinking.
So long, Straw Hat.
Tell your brother I said hello.
If he's still alive, I'll buy him a drink.
And by the way, thanks for being our live bait,
you little imbecile.
Glad to see they're safe.
Well, okay.
See ya.
Thanks a lot for your help, you guys.
Dad, he's so sweet.
My heart, it's breaking.
Stay sharp, men.
He's got a 300 million berry bounty.
This is our chance, run for it.
Right, let's go.
Look, I don't have time to fight all you guys right now.
Shougar.
Oh great, he's on a rampage.
He's on the run, after it.
The stairs to go down.
We're close.
Only a bit further and we'll arrive at the floor where Ace is being held.
Took long enough.
It feels like we've been riding in this elevator forever.
It just makes sense.
The area we're headed to must be isolated.
It's filled with the most dangerous criminals from all over the world,
not just firefist.
With inmates like these, we can't afford to take any chances.
We wouldn't be going to all this trouble if you weren't a warlord, you know.
Then it's fortunate that I am.
So you're more than happy to help me, aren't you?
No!
But of course!
Incidentally, there's a prisoner down here who was once a warlord just like you.
Well, I have no interest in him.
I only came here to see Firefist Ace.
I promise to behave.
And I intend to hold you to that.
So hot!
I think we're safe up here.
Their attention's on Straw Hat like we planned.
They've sealed off the staircases leading up.
And it's getting far too hot for me to remain here any longer.
Un-duh-craw! Un-duh-orah!
Huh?
Hey! Who's that singing?
Un-duh-craw! Un-duh-orah!
Huh?
Un-duh-orah!
They always say, it's all about the ways of boys and girls.
But I'm Special Cause I take the best from both worlds.
That's why we are always free.
So free!
Always free!
When you're queer, you never fear.
Never fear.
No!
Never fear!
Oh, come my way!
After much tribulation, Impel Down is put on lockdown,
and its only exit is sealed,
leaving Luffy's chances of success even lower than before.
Unaware of this, Luffy continues to ace his floor,
only to have another unexpected reunion.
On the next, One Piece! The Unleashed Swan!
A reunion with Bon Clay!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!